the San Antonio Spurs are now just one the San Antonio Spurs are now just one
step away from the prize that has been
step away from the prize that has been step away from the prize that has been
their goal all season long the NBA
their goal all season long the NBA their goal all season long the NBA
Championship tonight it's game five of
Championship tonight it's game five of Championship tonight it's game five of
the NBA Finals go SPS
the NBA Finals go SPS go it ends today get it done get it done go it ends today get it done get it done
tonight last year we're 30 seconds away
tonight last year we're 30 seconds away tonight last year we're 30 seconds away
way we have it in the bag and and it
way we have it in the bag and and it way we have it in the bag and and it
slips out of our fingers it's not over
slips out of our fingers it's not over slips out of our fingers it's not over
till it's over our goal right now is
till it's over our goal right now is till it's over our goal right now is
just to win one more game standing in
just to win one more game standing in just to win one more game standing in
the way is the two-time defending
the way is the two-time defending the way is the two-time defending
Champion heat a team that has used a
Champion heat a team that has used a Champion heat a team that has used a
two-day break between games to regroup
two-day break between games to regroup two-day break between games to regroup
and refocus I'm very confident I believe
and refocus I'm very confident I believe and refocus I'm very confident I believe
in our our guys I believe in our group
in our our guys I believe in our group in our our guys I believe in our group
and we look forward to trying to get
and we look forward to trying to get and we look forward to trying to get
this win
tonight head back to Miami R for game