Donald Trump is set to
accept a very pricey gift
from the royal family of Qatar,
taking delivery of a Boeing 747
that will be used as Air Force
One during his second term.
The very lavish gift is raising
substantial ethical and legal questions,
and we want to talk about it
now with Richard
Painter, former white House
ethics lawyer under George
W Bush
and professor of law
at the University of Minnesota.
Richard,
thank you very much
for being here with us
and kind of walking us through,
some questions around all of this.
This is
said to be the most expensive
gift ever bestowed on a U.S. leader.
It has a value of more than $400 million.
The attorney general and white House
counsel office
have said they believe it's okay legally.
Where do you come down in this?
How would you assess this?
This is legal,