so far. So, like these are my
friends. And mind if I take some video
of you? Sure. Hi. Okay. All right. These
are your friends. Yeah, I know these.
We've been to their house a lot. And
then, you know, this is just a public
access road. They the people who live
here have to hire I know the guy who
snowplows this road because the city
doesn't plow it. Okay. So, that's part
of it. And then, uh, you know, there's
like five or six houses on this street.
So basically, a lot of people in this
neighborhood walk their dogs down the
street because it's just flat and
convenient. And if you walk in the cove,
it's up and down, up and down. So most
people like to just, you know, have a
little stroll with their dog in the
morning or the evening. And no one has
ever said anything. And even So And so
you were surprised by this on Saturday.
Well, I was because I didn't know he was
back, you know. I didn't know that
Kentrella is back. So, I think I'm going
to bake him some cookies and bring over
there because we had such a nice chat
after his daughter. He thought he was a
nice guy. He's a very sweet kid. I mean,
he's really young, you know. I mean,
this is a very young person. Very, very
young person. Very kind. He called me
ma'am. I told him I've never listened to
his music. He said I don't recommend it.
That's what he said. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
He's a man I don't recommend it. He has
a southern accent. Why?